[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "And from what you're hearing and feeling, has the tornado passed close to you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "from", "what", "you", "'re", "hearing", "and", "feeling", ",", "has", "the", "tornado", "passed", "close", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "It's hard to tell.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "to", "tell", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Is that what you're hearing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "'re", "hearing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "What happened here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "I don't think so much that people ignored the warning.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "much", "that", "people", "ignored", "the", "warning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Brandon, what can you see right now?", "question_tokens": ["Brandon", ",", "what", "can", "you", "see", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "We are actually not (AUDIO GAP).", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "actually", "not", "(", "AUDIO", "GAP", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Moore"]}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "NNS", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "So, Brandon, just to confirm, you are heading towards Moore, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "Brandon", ",", "just", "to", "confirm", ",", "you", "are", "heading", "towards", "Moore", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "We are now -- yes, sir, we are heading right towards Moore.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "now", "--", "yes", ",", "sir", ",", "we", "are", "heading", "right", "towards", "Moore", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brandon", "Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Moore"]}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "Can you confirm that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "confirm", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "I cannot confirm a tornado in Moore.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "not", "confirm", "a", "tornado", "in", "Moore", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "And in terms of the strength and power of the storm that you're experiencing, how would you describe it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "strength", "and", "power", "of", "the", "storm", "that", "you", "'re", "experiencing", ",", "how", "would", "you", "describe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "This is a very powerful storm.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "a", "very", "powerful", "storm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "What kind of thing are you picking up on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "thing", "are", "you", "picking", "up", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "I cannot confirm on any sort of cars being flipped or I can confirm factual damage because we are right on a previous tornado path of damage, so I can't -- I can't figure out if that is previous damage or if that was current damage.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "not", "confirm", "on", "any", "sort", "of", "cars", "being", "flipped", "or", "I", "can", "confirm", "factual", "damage", "because", "we", "are", "right", "on", "a", "previous", "tornado", "path", "of", "damage", ",", "so", "I", "ca", "n't", "--", "I", "ca", "n't", "figure", "out", "if", "that", "is", "previous", "damage", "or", "if", "that", "was", "current", "damage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "What do we know about Moore itself in terms of whether a tornado has touched down?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "we", "know", "about", "Moore", "itself", "in", "terms", "of", "whether", "a", "tornado", "has", "touched", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "There was a confirmed tornado, it wasn't a particularly strong tornado.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "was", "a", "confirmed", "tornado", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "a", "particularly", "strong", "tornado", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "What can you tell me?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "It is a very serious situation.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "a", "very", "serious", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "What should they be doing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "they", "be", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Well, first of all, listen to the newscasters on the radio.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "listen", "to", "the", "newscasters", "on", "the", "radio", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Governor, are you hearing reports of injuries fatalities at this stage?", "question_tokens": ["Governor", ",", "are", "you", "hearing", "reports", "of", "injuries", "fatalities", "at", "this", "stage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "At this time, we are trying to get the highways cleared off.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "this", "time", ",", "we", "are", "trying", "to", "get", "the", "highways", "cleared", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Moore"]}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Have you picked up any intelligence about what may be happening there?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "picked", "up", "any", "intelligence", "about", "what", "may", "be", "happening", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, looking at a map right now, of the storm itself, it is lit up pretty good right over Moore.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "looking", "at", "a", "map", "right", "now", ",", "of", "the", "storm", "itself", ",", "it", "is", "lit", "up", "pretty", "good", "right", "over", "Moore", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "RBR", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Are those tornado sirens going off?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "those", "tornado", "sirens", "going", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "We have been dropping south away from the cell and they just keep reforming more tornadoes, more tornadoes back out to the west.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "been", "dropping", "south", "away", "from", "the", "cell", "and", "they", "just", "keep", "reforming", "more", "tornadoes", ",", "more", "tornadoes", "back", "out", "to", "the", "west", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "What are they?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "They are tornado sirens.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "are", "tornado", "sirens", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "What do you think the best course of action is for anybody in a car on one of these interstates?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "the", "best", "course", "of", "action", "is", "for", "anybody", "in", "a", "car", "on", "one", "of", "these", "interstates", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "You have to watch where you are and for awhile, being in your car is still the safest place.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "to", "watch", "where", "you", "are", "and", "for", "awhile", ",", "being", "in", "your", "car", "is", "still", "the", "safest", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Can you hear me?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "hear", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "What is going on where you are?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "on", "where", "you", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "We are about 10 miles south of Minco right now.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "about", "10", "miles", "south", "of", "Minco", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "In terms of damage that you've seen to vehicles or to property, what have you seen so far?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "damage", "that", "you", "'ve", "seen", "to", "vehicles", "or", "to", "property", ",", "what", "have", "you", "seen", "so", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", "CC", "TO", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "We did see a very large three story house with the whole top roof gone or the whole top second floor and roof gone.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "did", "see", "a", "very", "large", "three", "story", "house", "with", "the", "whole", "top", "roof", "gone", "or", "the", "whole", "top", "second", "floor", "and", "roof", "gone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Where will you be going to next?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "will", "you", "be", "going", "to", "next", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, since we can't really get on any of the main highways, I honestly don't know right this second.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "since", "we", "ca", "n't", "really", "get", "on", "any", "of", "the", "main", "highways", ",", "I", "honestly", "do", "n't", "know", "right", "this", "second", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "What is the state of play where you are?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "state", "of", "play", "where", "you", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "ANDOLPH: Absolutely chaos.", "answer_tokens": ["ANDOLPH", ":", "Absolutely", "chaos", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "-NONE-", ",", "-NONE-", ",", "-NONE-", ",", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "What is the best thing they can do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "best", "thing", "they", "can", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "The best thing for them to do is exit the interstate, whether it's I-40, I-240, I-35, exit the interstate and seek immediate shelter.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "best", "thing", "for", "them", "to", "do", "is", "exit", "the", "interstate", ",", "whether", "it", "'s", "I-40", ",", "I-240", ",", "I-35", ",", "exit", "the", "interstate", "and", "seek", "immediate", "shelter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "And in terms of people who may have been casualties, in terms of injuries or possibly even fatalities, what can you tell me?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "terms", "of", "people", "who", "may", "have", "been", "casualties", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "injuries", "or", "possibly", "even", "fatalities", ",", "what", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "RB", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "I don't -- I cannot confirm any numbers at this time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "can", "not", "confirm", "any", "numbers", "at", "this", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", ":", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "If people are literally jam-packed in what is being described as a parking lot on one of these interstates and they simply can't exit, what is the best thing they can do?", "question_tokens": ["If", "people", "are", "literally", "jam-packed", "in", "what", "is", "being", "described", "as", "a", "parking", "lot", "on", "one", "of", "these", "interstates", "and", "they", "simply", "ca", "n't", "exit", ",", "what", "is", "the", "best", "thing", "they", "can", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "The best thing for them to do, especially -- the winds like I said will suck them out of their car.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "best", "thing", "for", "them", "to", "do", ",", "especially", "--", "the", "winds", "like", "I", "said", "will", "suck", "them", "out", "of", "their", "car", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Have you in your time as a state trooper encountered anything quite like this?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "in", "your", "time", "as", "a", "state", "trooper", "encountered", "anything", "quite", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Have you heard that?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "heard", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Well, the way I understand it, I think you're correct, it's moved on past us.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "way", "I", "understand", "it", ",", "I", "think", "you", "'re", "correct", ",", "it", "'s", "moved", "on", "past", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNP", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJR", "VBG", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Can you tell me anything about that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "tell", "me", "anything", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Well, I think (INAUDIBLE) there is so much chatter going on, a lot of people responding to different things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "there", "is", "so", "much", "chatter", "going", "on", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "responding", "to", "different", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["El Reno"]}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Is that your view?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Not in El Reno.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "in", "El", "Reno", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "What are you seeing coming in at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "seeing", "coming", "in", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Right now, I don't have information on what we're seeing at the moment.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "now", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "information", "on", "what", "we", "'re", "seeing", "at", "the", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Are you anticipating having a lot of people in with a lot of injuries?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "anticipating", "having", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "in", "with", "a", "lot", "of", "injuries", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "What are you hearing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "hearing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "We actually saw that.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "actually", "saw", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "And, Mr. Mayor, in terms of damage to property or injuries to people in Moore, what can you tell me?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "Mr.", "Mayor", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "damage", "to", "property", "or", "injuries", "to", "people", "in", "Moore", ",", "what", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "I don't have a report back on that yet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "report", "back", "on", "that", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Mayor"], "LOCATION": ["Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Moore"]}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Is it your understanding that people may have been injured in Moore?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "your", "understanding", "that", "people", "may", "have", "been", "injured", "in", "Moore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Not so much in Moore.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "so", "much", "in", "Moore", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "And from other local reports that you're seeing, are they matching what the state trooper told me, that there have just been an extraordinary large number of crashes involving vehicles?", "question_tokens": ["And", "from", "other", "local", "reports", "that", "you", "'re", "seeing", ",", "are", "they", "matching", "what", "the", "state", "trooper", "told", "me", ",", "that", "there", "have", "just", "been", "an", "extraordinary", "large", "number", "of", "crashes", "involving", "vehicles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Yes, sir, that's what we're hearing.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sir", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "we", "'re", "hearing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "From what you're seeing and hearing, how bad is this on the ground?", "question_tokens": ["From", "what", "you", "'re", "seeing", "and", "hearing", ",", "how", "bad", "is", "this", "on", "the", "ground", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "It's extremely bad due to the time of day that it impacted the metro.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "extremely", "bad", "due", "to", "the", "time", "of", "day", "that", "it", "impacted", "the", "metro", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "CC", "CD", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Have you seen any local reports about the number of car accidents and crashes that have been happening tonight?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "seen", "any", "local", "reports", "about", "the", "number", "of", "car", "accidents", "and", "crashes", "that", "have", "been", "happening", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I haven't seen any reports but we've been tracking the storms throughout the day and we just in our vehicle probably checked at least three overturned vehicles on their tops and probably saw another three or four that were left just abandoned in roadway.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "seen", "any", "reports", "but", "we", "'ve", "been", "tracking", "the", "storms", "throughout", "the", "day", "and", "we", "just", "in", "our", "vehicle", "probably", "checked", "at", "least", "three", "overturned", "vehicles", "on", "their", "tops", "and", "probably", "saw", "another", "three", "or", "four", "that", "were", "left", "just", "abandoned", "in", "roadway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["El Reno"]}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Ben, in terms of the power and strength of this storm, how would you describe it to me?", "question_tokens": ["Ben", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "power", "and", "strength", "of", "this", "storm", ",", "how", "would", "you", "describe", "it", "to", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Well, it started off as just a single what we call super cell west of El Reno and it intensified into several super cells.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "started", "off", "as", "just", "a", "single", "what", "we", "call", "super", "cell", "west", "of", "El", "Reno", "and", "it", "intensified", "into", "several", "super", "cells", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "And where will you be headed now, Ben?", "question_tokens": ["And", "where", "will", "you", "be", "headed", "now", ",", "Ben", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "We're probably going to continue to head south until it's kind of a state of emergency in the metro area right now.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "probably", "going", "to", "continue", "to", "head", "south", "until", "it", "'s", "kind", "of", "a", "state", "of", "emergency", "in", "the", "metro", "area", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "What do you know about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "know", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Yes, you bring up a good point.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "bring", "up", "a", "good", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "Mr. Lamb, can you hear me?", "question_tokens": ["Mr.", "Lamb", ",", "can", "you", "hear", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Loud and clear.", "answer_tokens": ["Loud", "and", "clear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Lamb"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "What can you tell me, sir?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "tell", "me", ",", "sir", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Piers, it's early for assessment, I know you talked to highway patrol.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "it", "'s", "early", "for", "assessment", ",", "I", "know", "you", "talked", "to", "highway", "patrol", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "And as lieutenant governor of the state, how do you feel about the fact this is coming so soon after the devastation in Moore?", "question_tokens": ["And", "as", "lieutenant", "governor", "of", "the", "state", ",", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "fact", "this", "is", "coming", "so", "soon", "after", "the", "devastation", "in", "Moore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "AMB: Well, it's not easy.", "answer_tokens": ["AMB", ":", "Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "easy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "From what you're seeing and hearing, do you imagine there are many more casualties?", "question_tokens": ["From", "what", "you", "'re", "seeing", "and", "hearing", ",", "do", "you", "imagine", "there", "are", "many", "more", "casualties", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "I don't want to speculate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "speculate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Is the particular problem, do you think, what is happening on the interstates tonight?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "particular", "problem", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "what", "is", "happening", "on", "the", "interstates", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "Yes, most definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "most", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "What advice do you give people who may be stuck in their car on one of these interstates?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "do", "you", "give", "people", "who", "may", "be", "stuck", "in", "their", "car", "on", "one", "of", "these", "interstates", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Well, the most important thing is not to find yourself stuck in the water.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "most", "important", "thing", "is", "not", "to", "find", "yourself", "stuck", "in", "the", "water", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["St. Louis"]}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "How widespread is it now, do we believe?", "question_tokens": ["How", "widespread", "is", "it", "now", ",", "do", "we", "believe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "Well, you know, it does extend all the way on up toward St. Louis.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "does", "extend", "all", "the", "way", "on", "up", "toward", "St.", "Louis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "Is that your understanding?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "understanding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "Yes, that's what I think.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "I", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "Nick, what's going on there now?", "question_tokens": ["Nick", ",", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "there", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "The line is funneling out of the area.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "line", "is", "funneling", "out", "of", "the", "area", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "And in terms, again, of damage that you're seeing or hearing about, how would you describe it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "terms", ",", "again", ",", "of", "damage", "that", "you", "'re", "seeing", "or", "hearing", "about", ",", "how", "would", "you", "describe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "The house that we saw, it was definitely damaged.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "house", "that", "we", "saw", ",", "it", "was", "definitely", "damaged", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130531pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "Do you believe the worst has passed through El Reno now, in that area?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "the", "worst", "has", "passed", "through", "El", "Reno", "now", ",", "in", "that", "area", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "It definitely seems to be, looking at radar, there's nothing behind this building.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "definitely", "seems", "to", "be", ",", "looking", "at", "radar", ",", "there", "'s", "nothing", "behind", "this", "building", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["El Reno"]}}]